<resources>
    <string name="app_name">Land Of Gods</string>

    <!-- TODO: Remove or change this placeholder text -->
    <string name="hello_blank_fragment">Hello blank fragment</string>
    <string name="hill_station"> Stations</string>

    <!-- Category name for the vocabulary words for colors [CHAR LIMIT=20] -->
    <string name="trek_adventure">Adventure  </string>

    <!-- Category name for the vocabulary words for numbers [CHAR LIMIT=20] -->
    <string name="top_cusine">Top Cusine </string>

    <!-- Category name for the vocabulary words for family members [CHAR LIMIT=20] -->
    <string name="pilgrimages">Pilgrimages</string>
    <string name="Nainital">Nainital</string>
    <string name="aboutNainital">Known as the Lake District.It shines as a glittering jewel in the Himalayan Mountains and is surrounded with lakes and nature\'s bounty.</string>
    <string name="Auli">Auli</string>
    <string name="AboutAuli">Auli is considered among the best skiing destinations of India, it is situated in Chamoli district covering an elevation of  3,050 mts above sea level</string>
    <string name="Ranikhet">Ranikhet</string>
    <string name="aboutRanikhet">The hill station is Ranikhet, literally meaning - Queens Land. Ranikhet is a place that reflects the best of the great Himalayas.</string>
    <string name="Kausani">Kausani</string>
    <string name="aboutKausani">Kausani is known for offering a panoramic view of the massive Himalayan peaks such as Trishul, Nanda Devi</string>
    <string name="Pithoragarh">Pithoragarh</string>
    <string name="aboutPithoragarh">Located at an average elevation of 1,514 meters above sea level, Pithoragarh is a Himalayan town famous for it\'s heavenly beauty</string>
    <string name="Chaukori">Chaukori</string>
    <string name="aboutChaukori">As the name suggest Chaukori ia tiny hamlet shaped like  bowl that is enveloped in the heart of Himalaya</string>
    <string name="Mussoorie">Mussoorie</string>
    <string name="aboutMussoorie">The muse of a romantic, a loner’s wonderland and a nature lover’s paradise</string>
    <string name="kedarnath">Kedarnath</string>
    <string name="aboutKedarnath">Lies amidst the majestic snow-capped Himalayan ranges on the banks of river Mandakini</string>
    <string name="badrinath">Badrinath</string>
    <string name="aboutBadriNath">Perched at an average elevation of 3,300 metres.The town of Badrinath lies between Nar and Narayan mountain ranges</string>
    <string name="gangotri">Gangotri</string>
    <string name="aboutGangotri">Gangotri is a  town centered around the temple of Gangotri  it is belived that this is the place where river Ganga descended from heaven</string>
    <string name="yamunotri">Yamunotri</string>
    <string name="aboutYamunotri">Located at a height of 3293 metre above sea level this temple is dedicated to Goddess Yamuna</string>
    <string name="devprayag">Devprayag</string>
    <string name="aboutDevprayag">Devprayag is the last Prayag  of the Alaknanda River positioned at an elevation of 830 meters above sea level.</string>
    <string name="haridwar">Haridwar</string>
    <string name="aboutHaridwar">Revered as one among seven holiest places of India , Haridwar literally suggests the \'Gateway to Lord Vishnu\'</string>
    <string name="ukhimath">Ukhimath</string>
    <string name="aboutUkhimath">Situated at an elevation of 1317 mts above sea level revered as the home of Lord Kedarnath  during winters.</string>
    <string name="rishikesh">Rishikesh</string>
    <string name="aboutRishikesh">The celestial city of Rishikesh is a hermit’s hermitage, a sage’s abode The word Rishikesh literally suggests the \'locks or hairs of a sage\'</string>
    <string name="adiKailash">Adi Kailash</string>
    <string name="aboutAdikailash">Adi Kailash also referred to as Chota Kailash or Little Kailash situated in the Indian Territory in Pithoragarh district</string>
    <string name="Kafuli">Kafuli</string>
    <string name="aboutKafuli">Taste the famous blend of green leafy vegetables in the form of Kafuli</string>
    <string name="uradBada">Urad Bada</string>
    <string name="aboutUradBada">Kumaoni Dal Bade are crispy, flavoursome, gluten free urad dal fritters</string>
    <string name="Raita">Kheere Ka Raita</string>
    <string name="aboutRaita">A side dish prepared from curd, turmeric, grated cucumber, green chillies and mustard seeds, this raita can be had with just about everything</string>
    <string name="manduaKiRoti">Mandua Ki Roti</string>
    <string name="aboutManduaKiRoti">These delicious and nutritious chapatis are made from Mandua Flour (Finger</string>
    <string name="gahatKaParatha">Gahat Ka Paratha</string>
    <string name="aboutGahatKaPratha">Gahat ka paratha  is healthy and nutritious paratha stuffed with horse gram.</string>
    <string name="Singhal">Singhal</string>
    <string name="aboutSinghal">Singhals are part and parcel of Kumaon culture, a healthy delicacy made with semolina, banana, curd, milk, sugar, and cardamom.</string>
    <string name="phaanu">Phaanu</string>
    <string name="aboutPhaanu">A combination of different lentils like arhar, moong and urad soaked overnight, is what gives a unique taste to this complex dish</string>
    <string name="Singhori">Singori</string>
    <string name="aboutSinghori">This is a sweetmeat moulded in an indigenous leaf called malla ka patta that results in little cones fragrant with the elusive scent of cardamom</string>
    <string name="dubuk">Dubuk</string>
    <string name="aboutDubuk">This very traditional Kumaoni recipe is made of lentils, either bhatt, gehat or arhar, which are boiled and later separated from the stock.</string>
    <string name="gulgula">Gulgula</string>
    <string name="aboutGulgula">Gulgula is a delectable sweet of Uttarakhand. It is a sweet local snack made of jaggery which traces its origin to the Garhwal region.</string>
    <string name="kedarkantha">Kedarkantha</string>
    <string name="aboutKedarkantha">A trekker’s delight and rookie’s rite of passage,at a towering peak of 3800 meters,Kedarkantha is located in Govind Wildlife Sancttuary</string>
    <string name="kedartal">Kedartal</string>
    <string name="aboutKedartal">Kedartal also known as ‘Shiva’s Lake’ is one of the highest lakes(4912) metres above sea level in Uttarkashi district.</string>
    <string name="pindari">Pindari</string>
    <string name="aboutPindari">Situated in the mesmerizing Kumaon Himalayas, Pindari Glacier is a most accessible of all glacier treks</string>
    <string name="chopata">Chopata</string>
    <string name="aboutChopata">Also known as Switzeerland of Uttrakhand Chopta is a evergreen forest area which is a part of kedarnath wildlife sanctuary</string>
    <string name="deoriTal">DeoriTal</string>
    <string name="aboutDeoriTal">Devariyatal is an emerald lake perched at a height of 2438 mts above sea level , it falls under Kedarnath Musk Deer Wildlife Sanctuary .</string>
    <string name="bungee">Bungee Jumping</string>
    <string name="aboutBungee">Located at a distance of 15 km from Lakshman Jhula in Rishikesh, a small village named Mohan Chatti is a hotspot for bungee jumping in India.</string>
    <string name="riverRafting">River Rafting</string>
    <string name="aboutRiverRAFTING">The enticing city of Rishikesh hosts a range of rafting activities With Grade I to V rapids, this place is an ideal destination for both amateurs and professionals</string>
    <string name="paragliding">Paragliding</string>
    <string name="aboutParaggliding">Uttarakhand offers abundant operations for paragliding for those looking for the rush of flying paragliding flights are offered via  specialists at Mukteshwar and Ranikhet.</string>
    <string name="skiing">Skiing</string>
    <string name="aboutSkiing">Skiing is one of the most enthralling  activities in Uttarakhand . The snow-covered mountain peaks of Auli are the best to experience this thrilling activity.</string>
</resources>
